High in this video we are going to talk about stack abstract data types.
So let's get started.
And as I said earlier it is an abstract data type.
We usually represent abstract data types with interfaces for example in Java.
The basic operations are the Pope the push and the peak.
It has a so-called lethal structure which means that Last In First Out.
So the last item the insert is going to be the first item we take out.
It's very important that in the most high level of programming languages that can be easily implemented
either with arrays or linguists and a number of programming languages are stack oriented meaning they
define the most basic operations.
For example are adding two numbers printing a corrector on the concert or so on as taking their arguments
from the stack and placing any return values back on the stack.
So for example we have this push operation.
We put the given item to the top of the stack.
It is a very simple operation.
It can be done in Ordover and so cost on time complexity.
So we would like to push the 12 on the stack we just insert it then we push the 56.
We are going to put it on the top of the 12.
We are going to push 88.
It's going to be the next item we pushing through the stack.
Ok so the push operation is basically adding items to the stack.
What about the pop operation.
We take the last item we have inserted to the top of the stack.
This is the so-called life force structure.
As I said earlier.
So the last item we have inserted will be the first item we take out.
It's a very simple operation.
It can be done also in Costanzo or don't want time complexity.
So if we call this Taggert poop it's going to pull up the last item or inserted and we inserted the
88.
So that's why it's going to be pulled out of the stack.
Ok what if we call the pop method again.
Then it's going to pop out the next item which is the 56.
So what about the cooperation.
It's going to return the item from the top of the stack without removing it.
It's again a very simple operation it can be done in constant time complexity.
So what's the difference between the peak and pop method the pop matter is going to remove the last
item from the stack.
The peak method is going to show.
So it's going to return the value of the last item without removing it.
So the size the items in the stack is not going to change.
OK.
So if we call the peek method is just going to return 88.
But the structure of the stack remains the same which means that we are not going to remove 88.
We're just going to take the well-you.
So what about the applications of stack abstract data type.
Of course in stack oriented programming languages we can use Ptak as an abstract data type.
And lots of lots of Grof algorithms that relies heavily on stack abstract data types such as that data
for search can be implemented with the map of stacks.
OK we can implement it.
We have of recursion but we can implement it.
We have stacks as well.
Or finding the oil or cycles in a graph relies heavily on stack abstract data type or finding strongly
connected components in a graph.
For example for Cazayoux algorithm we definitely have to use stack as an underlying abstract data type.
So basically that's all about stacks in the main.
Thanks for watching.